Guide to the William Rufus Shafter Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series VII - Printed Reference
  - Copies (Box 8, Folder 80)
Mexican Constitutional Army Roll I Folder 5
Mexico, (Country) Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 7 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 33, Folder 35, Folder 36
México (Spanish Steamer) Roll IV Folder 32 Roll V Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 55
Miami (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 38, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 52
Miantonomok (U. S. Ship) Roll I Folder 10
Michigan Historical Magazine Roll VI Folder 57
Michigan (U. S. Ship) Roll IV Folder 38
Michler, Francis Lt.Col., A. A. G. Roll II Folder 12 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20
Midwinter Exposition, San Francisco Roll V Folder 41
Miles, Nelson A. Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 8, Folder 9, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 43, Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 54, Folder 55, Folder 57
Miley, John D. Lt., Maj., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 9, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 55, Folder 57
Miller, Robert Roll II Folder 13
Miller T. W. Roll IV Folder 40
Mills, Andrew Roll III Folder 20
Mills, Samuel M. Maj. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 16 Roll V Folder 47
Miner, Charles W. Maj. Roll II Folder 12 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34, Folder 37
The Miner's Journal Roll V Folder 43
Minnewaska (U. S. Ship) Roll V Folder 44
Miranda, Francesco Roll I Folder 7 Roll V Folder 44
Mission Fight Roll I Folder 8
Mississippi Roll III Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 44, Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 49
Missouri, Department of Roll I Folder 8 Roll V Folder 45, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 53
Mobile, Alabama Roll II Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 22, Folder 26
Mobile (U. S. Ship) Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44
Mohawk (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 26 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 43, Folder 44
Monroe, Fort Roll III Folder 22, Folder 25 Roll IV Folder 36, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 47, Folder 48
Montauk Point, Long Island, New York Roll II Folder 11 Roll IV Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 53, Folder 57
Montauk Steamboat Company Roll V Folder 46
Montgomery, Frank H. Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 54
Moore, Mary E. Roll V Folder 42
Moore, W. S. Roll II Folder 17
More, Robert D. Roll II Folder 18
Morgan, John T. Senator Roll II Folder 14
Morgan (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 57
Morrison, John F. Lt. Roll IV Folder 38
Morro Castle Roll III Folder 21, Folder 24 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 36 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 54, Folder 57
Morro, Cuba Roll II Folder 17 Roll III Folder 22, Folder 25 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 33, Folder 36 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 54
Mortero (Spanish Ship) Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 35 Roll V Folder 42
Mosher, Theodore Capt. Roll IV Folder 30
Moulton, J. Warriner Roll III Folder 23
Movilizados Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 38
Mucks, [?] Roll I Folder 8
Muller, [?] Roll I Folder 4
Muñoz, Mariana Roll VI Folder 52
Muñoz-Corralba, Antonio Roll IV Folder 37 Roll VI Folder 52
Munson, Fred L Lt. Roll IV Folder 37
Murfresboro, Tennessee Roll I Folder 1
Murphy, Kate Roll I Folder 8
Murphy, Sue Roll I Folder 8
Naranjo, Felipe Roll I Folder 5
Nashville, Battle of Roll I Folder 1 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 54, Folder 57
Nashville (U. S. Ship) Roll IV Folder 38
National Club Hospital Roll V Folder 44
National Peace Jubilee Roll V Folder 40
Naval Intelligence, Office of Roll I Folder 9 Roll III Folder 19
Navarro, Angel Roll III Folder 25
Navy, Department of the Roll I Folder 9 Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 34, Folder 40 Roll VI Folder 52
Navy Register Roll VI Folder 52
Navy, U. S. Roll II Folder 12 Roll III Folder 21, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 29 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 53
Neutrality Laws Roll I Folder 5
Newgarden, George J. Roll VI Folder 54
Newman, Stephen I. Roll V Folder 45
New Orleans (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 21, Folder 26 Roll VI Folder 52
New York Roll I Folder 8, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13 Roll III Folder 25, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 46, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 53
New York Central and Hudson River Railroad Company Roll V Folder 46, Folder 48
New York City Roll II Folder 14 Roll III Folder 20 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 45, Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 49
New York Filter Manufactoring Company Roll V Folder 40
New York Herald (Newspaper) Roll III Folder 21 Roll IV Folder 51
New York Journal (Newspaper) Roll III Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 34
New York Press (Newspaper) Roll II Folder 16
New York Sun (Newspaper) Roll IV Folder 31 Roll VI Folder 53
New York Times (Newspaper) Roll III Folder 27
New York Herald (Newspaper) Roll III Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 41 Roll V Folder 45
New York (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33
Nicaragua Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 53
Nicholl, [?] Col., British Army, 1777 Roll I Folder 8
Nichols, Francis H. Newsman Roll V Folder 41
Nichols, M. W. Roll IV Folder 35
Nickerson, A. Howe Roll VI Folder 53
Nilson, Elgar Roll VI Folder 53
Nimrod (U. S. Tug) Roll III Folder 22
Nineteenth Michigan Volunteer Infantry Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8 Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 54, Folder 56, Folder 57
Nineteenth Infantry Roll I Folder 2, Folder 3 Roll III Folder 19
Ninth Cavalry Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 26, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 45, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 52
Ninth Infantry Roll II Folder 13, Folder 18, Folder 19 Roll III Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 52
Ninth Massachusetts Volunteer Infantry Roll III Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 33, Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 49
Noble, Robert H. Maj., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 9, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 35, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 52, Folder 55
Nolt, J. J. Roll I Folder 7
Non Combatants Roll III Folder 25
Noonan, [?] Judge Roll I Folder 5
Nordenfeldt, R. F. Roll V Folder 45
Norris, Frank Roll VII Folder 65
North American Trust Company Roll IV Folder 33 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 44
North Atlantic Squadron U. S. N. Roll I Folder 9 Roll V Folder 41 Roll VI Folder 52
Northern Continental Army of Bennington and Stillwater Roll I Folder 8
Norvell, Stevens T. Roll II Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 36
Norwegian Consul Roll III Folder 24
Nue, Frank E. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12
Nueces, District of Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7, Folder 8
Nueces (U. S. Transport) Roll V Folder 44, Folder 45
Nuncio, P. Col., Mex. Forces Roll I Folder 5
Nunez, [?] Gen., Cuban Forces Roll I Folder 10, Folder 11
Nuttman, Lewis Lt. Roll IV Folder 37
O'Brian, Lyster M. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Ocean Steamship Company Roll IV Folder 40
Ogden, Wesley Roll I Folder 8
Olivette (U. S. Ship) Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 25, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 35, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 52
Omaja Exposition Roll IV Folder 38 Roll V Folder 48
One hundred fifty-seventh Indiana Volunteer Infantry Roll II Folder 17
Ord, Edward O. C. Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 7, Folder 8 Roll III Folder 25
Ord, Edward O. C., Jr. A. D. C. Roll I Folder 2
Ord, James T. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 45, Folder 47
Order of Battle North Atlantic Station, U. S. N. Roll III Folder 21
Oregon (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 21 Roll VI Folder 52
Orleman, Louis H. Lt. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 7
Orizaba (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 38, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 44, Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 52
Osceola (U. S. Tugboat) Roll I Folder 9 Roll II Folder 12 Roll III Folder 21 Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 52
Otis, Harrison Gray Col. Roll I Folder 8
Pacha, H. Enver Gen., Turkish Army Roll VI Folder 52
Pacific, Department of Roll II Folder 13 Roll VI Folder 53
Pacific, Division of the Roll II Folder 16
Pacificos Roll III Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 34, Folder 36
Page, John H. Col. Roll I Folder 10 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 50
Paget, [?] Capt., Naval Attache, England Roll VI Folder 52
Palma, T. Estrada Gen. Roll I Folder 10
Palma, Cuba Roll III Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 34, Folder 36 Roll V Folder 42 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 57
Palmer, John Sect. of State Roll V Folder 47
Pando, [?] Gen., Cuban Forces Roll III Folder 22, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 36 Roll VI Folder 52
Panther (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16
Paredes, Jose de Capt., Sp. Forces Roll VI Folder 57
Parena, Julian Collector of Customs, Santiago Roll IV Folder 35
Parker, John H. Lt. Roll IV Folder 31 Roll V Folder 43
Parker, William M. Private Roll V Folder 45
Parkhurst, Charles Capt. Roll VI Folder 57 Roll VII Folder 65
Parks, Juno W. Roll III Folder 26
Paschal, George Roll I Folder 5, Folder 7, Folder 8
Patterson, John H. Lt. Col. Roll II Folder 12 Roll V Folder 47
Patton, Jonathan N. Capt. Roll V Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49
Paxton, Robert G. Lt. Roll II Folder 13
Pearce, John S. Gen. Roll I Folder 4
Pearson, Edward P. Brig. Gen. Roll III Folder 24 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50, Folder 52
Peck, T. S. A. G., I. G. Roll I Folder 8
Pecos Bill Roll I Folder 2 Roll VI Folder 55, Folder 57
Pecos River Roll I Folder 2, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7 Roll IV Folder 37
Peninsular Campaign Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8
Penn, Julius A. Lt. Roll II Folder 13
Pennsylvania Railway Roll V Folder 48
Penrose, Charles B. Roll I Folder 5
Perara, Alfredo Roll IV Folder 30
Perara, Oscar Roll IV Folder 30
Pereja, Felix Gen., Sp. Forces Roll IV Folder 34, Folder 35 Roll V Folder 42
Perez, Pedro Gen., Cuban Forces Roll IV Folder 33, Folder 35, Folder 38
Perkins, George C. Gov., California, 1879 - 1883 Roll I Folder 8
Pershing, [?] Lt. Roll IV Folder 39
Petersburg, Virginia, Battle of Roll VI Folder 54
Petrat, George H. Lt., U. S. N. Roll I Folder 9
Pettibone Brothers, Manufactoring Company Roll II Folder 12
Pfieffer, George W. Roll III Folder 26
Phelan, James D. Mayor of San Francisco Roll V Folder 45
Philadelphia (U. S. Ship) Roll IV Folder 36 Roll V Folder 44
Philippine Islands Roll II Folder 13 Roll VI Folder 51, Folder 53, Folder 54
St. Phillip, Fort Roll II Folder 11
Phillips, William A. Lt. Roll VI Folder 50
Philton (Spanish Ship) Roll III Folder 22
Phoenix, Arizona Roll VI Folder 53
Pina, Dr. [?] Roll VI Folder 58
Pinar del Rio Roll I Folder 9 Roll IV Folder 36
Plant, Henry B. President of Plant System Roll II Folder 18
Plant System of Railways and Steamship Lines Roll II Folder 18
Platt, Thomas C. Senator, New York Roll III Folder 22
Playa del Este, Cuba Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44
Plummer, Edward H. Capt. Roll III Folder 27, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36 Roll V Folder 45, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 53, Folder 55
Point, Fort (Galveston, Texas) Roll II Folder 11
Poland, John S. Brig. Gen. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 13
Polk County Fair Association Florida Roll II Folder 18 Roll V Folder 46
Polk, Burr H. Capt., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 1
Ponce, Porto Rico Roll IV Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 45, Folder 47
Poore, Benjamin A. Lt. Roll II Folder 16
Pope, Benjamin F. Lt. Col. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 34 Roll VI Folder 51
Pope, James W. Maj., Quartermaster Roll II Folder 13
Porter, Fitz John Gen. Roll II Folder 14
Porter, William L. A. A. G. Roll I Folder 1
Porto Rico Roll III Folder 27, Folder 30 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 52, Folder 53
Porto Rico Battalion Roll III Folder 23, Folder 27
Port Tampa Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 23, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 51, Folder 57
Portuguese Consul, Ros, Modesto Roll IV Folder 25
Port Victor (U. S. Ship) Roll IV Folder 36, Folder 38, Folder 39
Potomac, Army of the Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 54, Folder 57
Potter, William W. Roll VI Folder 57
Powell, William H. Col. Roll II Folder 18
Pozo House Roll III Folder 25
Prairie (U. S. Ship) Roll IV Folder 38 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44
Prairie Seminary, Richland County Roll VI Folder 57
Presidio del Rio Grandes Roll I Folder 4
Preston, Mr. and Mrs. Formerly Mrs. Grover Cleveland Roll VI Folder 55
Provisional Battalion of Puerto Rico #1 Roll VI Folder 52
Price, Harrison J. Capt. Roll I Folder 8 Roll IV Folder 37 Roll VI Folder 50
Price, William R. Maj. Roll I Folder 2
Princessa (Spanish Ship) Roll III Folder 25
Prisoners, Spanish Roll IV Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40, Folder 41 Roll V Folder 42
Proctor, Redfield Asst. to the Sect. of War Roll I Folder 8
Pullman, John W. Lt. Roll I Folder 7, Folder 8
Punta Gorda Battery Roll III Folder 24, Folder 31, Folder 45
Purdy, Clarence N. Roll V Folder 48, Folder 49
Purgitorio Bridge Roll IV Folder 35, Folder 40
Puritan (U. S. Ship) Roll I Folder 10
Quail, J. N. Roll V Folder 46
Quay, Andrew G. C. Capt. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 18
Quesada, [?] Roll I Folder 10
Quinine Roll III Folder 13 Roll IV Folder 39
Quinly, William E. Roll I Folder 8
Rabi, [?] Gen., Cuban Forces Roll III Folder 21, Folder 29 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 57
Rafferty, William H. Maj. Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 36 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44
Ramolina, Texas Roll I Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 6
Ramsey, Frank D. Lt. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 33
Ramsey, Robert H. Bvt. Col., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 1
Rand, Carles F. Roll III Folder 26
Rand, G. F. President of Sp. American Iron Company Roll I Folder 9
Randall, Fort (South Dakota) Roll I Folder 8 Roll IV Folder 38 Roll V Folder 45, Folder 47
Randall, George M. Brig. Gen. Roll V Folder 45, Folder 47
Randolf, Wallace F. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 14 Roll III Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 45, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 52
Ransom, Roswell Roll VI Folder 53
Rathom, John R. Roll II Folder 14
Rawson, Stephen Roll VI Folder 53
Ray, Juan Spy Roll I Folder 4
Rea, George Bronson Newsman Roll III Folder 19
Read, George N. Lt. Roll II Folder 12
Reade, Philip Maj. Roll IV Folder 37 Roll VI Folder 54
Reeve, Horace M. Lt. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Reeves, James H. Lt. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Regan, James Capt. Roll IV Folder 38, Folder 40
Regular Army and Navy Union Roll I Folder 8
Reina de Los Angeles (Spanish Steamer) Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 35, Folder 36
Reina Mercedes (Spanish Ship) Roll I Folder 9 Roll III Folder 22 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 54
Relfe, Julian Roll VI Folder 52
Relief (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 26, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 32, Folder 36, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 46, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 53
Remembrance (English Ship) Roll IV Folder 38
Remey, George C. Commodore, U. S. N. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30
Reno, Fort (Oaklahoma) Roll VI Folder 49
Resolute (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 40 Roll V Folder 43
Revolutionary War Roll I Folder 8 Roll VI Folder 56
Revolutionists, Mexican Roll I Folder 3, Folder 5
Rhodes, Charles D. Maj. Gen. Roll VI Folder 57
Rice, F. C., Esquire Roll VI Folder 50
Richards, De Forest Roll VI Folder 53
Richards, John T. Roll V Folder 48
Ringgold, Fort (Texas) Roll I Folder 2
Rings, R. E. Roll III Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30
Rio Grande (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34 Roll V Folder 42 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 54
Rittman, F. E. Auditor, War Department Roll VI Folder 54
Rivers, T. R. Roll III Folder 25
Robertson, Edgar B. Maj. Roll IV Folder 34
Robinson, [R. Q.?] Maj. Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 36 Roll V Folder 43
Rochester, William B. Paymaster Roll I Folder 1
Rodgers, John I. Brig. Gen., Vols. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 18
Rodler, J. Lt., Naval Attache, Austro-Hungary Roll VI Folder 52
Rodriquez, I. Col., Cuban Forces Roll I Folder 7 Roll III Folder 24
Rodriquez, Jose Maria Guide Roll I Folder 5
Rodriquez, Pedro Guide Roll I Folder 4
Roque, Jose Oro Spanish deserter Roll III Folder 26
Romer, Manuel Capt., Sp. Forces Roll III Folder 25
Roosevelt, Theodore Lt. Col. Roll III Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 54, Folder 55, Folder 57
Root, Elihu Sect. of War Roll VI Folder 53, Folder 54
Rosell, Jose M. Col., Sp. Forces Roll IV Folder 34
Ros, Leonardo Gov. of Cuba Roll V Folder 42
Rossell, Ernesto Lt. Col., Cuban Forces Roll III Folder 29
Roudiez, Leon S. Maj. Roll II Folder 11, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 22, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 40, Folder 41, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 51, Folder 55
Rough Riders Roll II Folder 17 Roll III Folder 26, Folder 28 Roll VI Folder 51, Folder 54, Folder 57
Roumania (U. S. Steamer) Roll V Folder 47, Folder 48
Round Robin Letter Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 54, Folder 57
Rowan, A. S. Roll VI Folder 54
Ruger, Thomas H. Brig. Gen. Roll I Folder 8
Ruis, [?] Gen., Cuban Forces Roll II Folder 22
Rush Medical College Roll V Folder 45
Russia Roll II Folder 16
Ruthers, George W. Maj. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34, Folder 35
Sabinilla and Marota Railroad Roll I Folder 9
Sada, Jose Roll V Folder 54
Sagasta, Praxedes Mateo Sp. President of Ministers Roll V Folder 43
Saqua de Tenamo, Cuba Roll II Folder 18 Roll III Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43
Saint Louis (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 52
Saint Paul (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42
Salcedo, [?] Gen. Roll III Folder 29
Salcedo of Cuevas, Antonio Roll V Folder 41, Folder 43
Sample, William R. Capt., A. A. G. Roll IV Folder 37
Sampson, William T. Rear Admiral Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 38 Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 54, Folder 57
San Augustin (Spanish Ship) Roll IV Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 39
Sanders, William A. Roll IV Folder 34
Sandwich Islands, Hawaii Roll VI Folder 54
San Francisco, California Roll I Folder 8 Roll II Folder 13, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 21, Folder 26 Roll V Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 57
San Francisco Cronicle Roll V Folder 41
San Francisco Memorial Museum Roll V Folder 41
San Francisco Presidio, Fort Mason Roll VI Folder 53
San Francisco (Spanish Ship) Roll IV Folder 39
San Ignacio Loyola (Spanish Ship) Roll IV Folder 39
San Juan Roll III Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34, Folder 36 Roll V Folder 41 Roll VI Folder 54
San Juan, Battle of Roll III Folder 27
San Juan, Castle of Roll VI Folder 53
San Juan Fort Roll III Folder 26, Folder 28
San Juan Hill Roll III Folder 24 Roll V Folder 42 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 53, Folder 57
San Juan (Spanish Ship) Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 35, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 44
San Juan, Porto Rico Roll VI Folder 52
San Juan River, Cuba Roll II Folder 18 Roll III Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 26, Folder 29 Roll VI Folder 53, Folder 57
San Luis, Cuba, Surrender of Roll IV Folder 32
San Marcos (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 36 Roll V Folder 52
Santa Ana, Church of Roll III Folder 28
Santa Clara, Cuba (Province) Roll I Folder 9 Roll VI Folder 57
Santa Cruz del Sur, Cuba Roll I Folder 9
Santander, Spain Roll IV Folder 33
Santa Ursula, Fort Roll III Folder 22, Folder 27
Santiago Campaign Roll V Folder 45, Folder 47, Folder 49 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 54, Folder 55, Folder 56
Santiago de Cuba Roll I Folder 9 Roll II Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 54, Folder 55, Folder 57
Santiago de Cuba Archbishop Sáenz de Urtui y Crespo, Fco. 1894 - 1899 Roll III Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 37
Santiago, Department of Roll IV Folder 40 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43 Roll VI Folder 52
Santiago, Province of Roll V Folder 41, Folder 43
Santiago (U. S. Ship) Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34, Folder 38, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 52
Santos Agent Roll I Folder 2, Folder 6
Saratoga (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34, Folder 36, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46
Sargent, Herbert H. Col. Roll IV Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43 Roll VI Folder 55
Savage Station, Battle of Roll I Folder 1 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 52, Folder 54
Sawyer, James E. Maj. Roll V Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50
Schafter, Antoinette and Jules Roll VI Folder 53
Schley, Winfield S. Rear Admiral, U. S. N. Flying Squadron Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 22 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 57
Schofield, George W. Col. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7